mywellnessclub.in 2013-04-25

# Privacy Policy Mywellnessclub : health and wellness | beauty| women| recipes | travel | Online ads

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Agate Technocomcom Pvt Ltd collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [mywellnessclub.in](http://mywellnessclub.in/ "MyWellNessClub") website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Agate Technocomcom Pvt Ltd.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Agate Technocomcom Pvt Ltd may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_ Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize user experience_ We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_ We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_ We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Regarding Online Mobile RechargeÂ  **

Online Recharge will be done within 2 hours in case if any user face problem while payment please complaint at [here](http://mywellnessclub.in/mobile-recharge-feedback/ "Mobile recharge feedback"). Since we have tie-up with third party API services so they are the responsile person to refund the amount to us. As soon as we recive the amout from our third party service provider within 72 hours user will get re-funded from our end.

Mywellnessclub online mobile recharge will not collect Sensitive Information from individuals except with consent and only where it is necessary. Mywellnessclub will not collect Personal Data of any Individual in any underhanded manner.Â 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Classified Ads**

Ads which are posted in our classified section areÂ  fully customer’s responsibility. In case we monitor that any ad which is illegal, wrong information provided by customer or if we get any negative feedback regarding any ads in our portal, we have full power to take a initiative against that particular ad and we also unpublished the wrong ad.

**Source**

IBN Live for Political News

Fashion TV and Santa Banta for Entertainment

Indiafoodfreak.com for Restaurant Reviews

ESPN and Sky Sports for News related to Sports and Events

Zigwheel.com for Automobile Information

Magicbriks.com for Real Estate Details

Images and Data provided by above mention providers.

Other Images Courtesy Google.com

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Agate Technocomcom Pvt Ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

We have full right to moderate any comments which we found is not helpful for our website. Though we appreciate their valuable time and views

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://mywellnessclub.in/terms-condition "MyWellNessClub- Terms & Conditions"). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Agate Technocom Pvt. Ltd.  
Flat No.-102,AE-41,Vikram, AA-1,  
Newtown,  
Kolkata-156,

+91 33 3358 5000

contact@agatetechnocom.com

This document was last updated on February 02, 2013
